你需要记住的是
The most important thing you have to remember is that
每次你传输数据的时候，无论数据量多小
every time you transfer data, no matter how small, the radio
无线电都要运作至少半分钟
could stay powered up for nearly half a minute. So every
所以你的决策要基于
decision you make will be based on minimizing the number of
尽量减少传输的次数的原则上。当然了也有一种折衷的选择
times that this happens. But of course there's a balance here.
你想一次下载当前情况下
You want to download all the data a user is likely
用户可能需要的数据
to need for the current section in a single burst over
但是，你肯定不想把全部都下载下来
a single connection at full capacity. But of course, you don't
这样完全是浪费电量，下下来了一大堆
just want to pull down everything wasting battery power and bandwidth
可能永远用不到的数据
downloading data that's never going to be used. Now I could go
这里要是展开来我能讲一小时，不过Dan快等不及了
on for hours on this topic, but Dan's getting impatient. And
你能从他那儿学到怎样去实现上面这些关于传输优化的技能
you can learn the details on how to implement each of
包括预读取、
these best practices, including pre-fetching,
成批打包数据、减少你的更新频率
batching and bundling, burying your
和最小化载荷，通过一系列开发视频
update frequency, and minimizing your payloads by watching the series of
或者是读下面链接里的开发者指南
Dev Lite videos or reading the developer guides linked to in
现在在我将工作交给Dan
the instructor notes below. Now before I leave it to Dan
让他给你们展示怎样实现一个Sunshine的
to show you how to implement a sync adapter for
采用了一大堆我刚刚说过的最佳实践的同步adapter之前
Sunshine that takes advantage of a lot of the best practices
让我们想想如果你去开发一个App像是新闻阅读器，
I just described, let's consider what the best practice would be
什么才是最佳的实现方法
if you were building something like a news reader app. How
当这个App第一次被启动时，应该下载多少数据
much data should you download when the app is first started?
只下载主页面需要的标题、头版新闻里的所有文字和图片、
Just the front page of headlines, all the stories and images
所有新闻的文字（不包括图片）
linked to from that front page? Every story available, but none
还是现在可以取得的所有新闻的文字和图片？
of the images? Or every story and every image currently available?